(She's the girl in the PPT! She is. How shameless!)
(إنها الفتاة في PPT! إنها. يا لها من وقاحة!)
(She's gross.)
(إنها مقرفة).
(She does anything for money. Shame on her.)
(إنها تفعل أي شيء مقابل المال. عار عليها).
That's her. That's her.
تلك هي.  تلك هي.
(She doesn't appear to be so shameless.) I really didn't know she was shameless.
(لا يبدو أنها وقحة للغاية). لم أكن أعرف حقًا أنها كانت وقحة.
That's her.
تلك هي.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
What on earth are you talking about?
عن أي شيء تتحدث؟
You don't know what you did?
لا تعرف ماذا فعلت؟
Clarify it.
وضح ذلك.
Oops.
أُووبس.
Why did your lunch fall by itself?
لماذا سقط غدائك من تلقاء نفسه؟
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
Are you nuts?
هل انت مجنون؟
Oh my God.
يا إلهي.
Dear me.
عزيزي.
You...
أنت...
Clarify it.
وضح ذلك.
Don't bother to go after them.
لا تهتم بمطاردتهم.
I know what they talked about.
أعرف ما تحدثوا عنه.
=My Honey=
= حبيبي =
=EP14 Unexpected Love Battle=
= EP14 معركة حب غير متوقعة =
What?
ماذا؟
Su Ziying hooked up with a rich boy?
سو Ziying مدمن مخدرات مع صبي غني؟
Shh.
صه.
Keep your voice down,
حافظ على صوتك منخفضًا ،
or the whole school would hear you.
أو المدرسة كلها تسمعك.
Come on.
هيا.
How could Su Ziying hook up with a rich guy?
كيف يمكن لـ Su Ziying التواصل مع رجل ثري؟
I mean...
أعني...
Why did she do that?
لماذا فعلت ذلك؟
That guy even made a PPT to cook up the story.
حتى أن هذا الرجل صنع PPT لطهي القصة.
That's strange.
هذا غريب.
Not exactly.
ليس تماما.
Even an errant man likes to apologize with a PPT.
حتى الرجل الضال يحب أن يعتذر باستخدام PPT.
(White Paper for How a Material Girl Seduced a Rich Boy)
(مستند تعريفي تمهيدي حول كيفية إغراء فتاة مادية لصبي غني)
Also, this guy used "seduced",
أيضًا ، استخدم هذا الرجل كلمة "مغوي" ،
instead of "hooked up".
بدلاً من "التوصيل".
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll check out who made this PPT.
سوف تحقق من الذي صنع هذا PPT.
Right.
الصحيح.
Let's find him
لنجده
and screw him.
وأفسده.
Some information is true.
بعض المعلومات صحيحة.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
Ye Juncheng and I have some money trading.
يي جونتشنغ ولدي بعض المال في التداول.
Ziying,
تسيينغ ،
where are you going?
إلى أين تذهب؟
To work.
للعمل.
I won't stop working
لن أتوقف عن العمل
unless I die.
إلا إذا أموت.
Come on.
هيا.
Why is she so unmindful?
لماذا هي غير مبالية جدا؟
Whoever started the trouble must end it.
من بدأ المشكلة يجب أن ينهيها.
I'll ask Ye Juncheng to solve the problem.
سأطلب من Ye Juncheng حل المشكلة.
When did you friend him on WeChat?
متى صديقته على WeChat؟
Are you acquainted with him?
هل تعرفه؟
This isn't the point, okay?
هذا ليس هو الهدف ، حسنًا؟
Hello, Miss.
مرحبا يا انسة.
What would you like?
ماذا تحب؟
You don't look very beautiful.
أنت لا تبدين جميلة جدا.
Who are you looking for?
على من تبحث؟
Where's Ye Juncheng?
أين يي جونتشنغ؟
Aren't you together?
ألستم معا
Ye Juncheng isn't here.
يي جونتشنغ ليس هنا.
If you want to talk to him...
إذا كنت تريد التحدث معه ...
I want to talk to you.
أريد أن أتحدث إليك.
Let's talk somewhere else.
لنتحدث في مكان آخر.
What do you think?
ماذا تعتقد؟
Do you like the PowerPoint I made for you?
هل يعجبك برنامج PowerPoint الذي صنعته لك؟
So, it's you.
إذن ، أنت.
Mm.
مم.
I forgot to introduce myself.
لقد نسيت أن أقدم نفسي.
I'm Hua Yun.
أنا هوا يون.
I study business abroad.
أنا أدرس الأعمال في الخارج.
I am
انا
Ye Juncheng's fiancée.
يي جونتشنغ خطيبة.
I grew up with him.
لقد نشأت معه.
We're typical childhood sweethearts.
نحن أحباء عاديون في مرحلة الطفولة.
We're family friends, too.
نحن أصدقاء العائلة أيضًا.
I study business abroad
أنا أدرس الأعمال في الخارج
just to help Ye Juncheng with his business later.
فقط لمساعدة Ye Juncheng في عمله لاحقًا.
A poor student like you can't be as good as me.
لا يمكن لطالب فقير مثلك أن يكون جيدًا مثلي.
Besides,
بجانب،
a humble girl like you wants to marry such a rich guy?
فتاة متواضعة مثلك تريد الزواج من مثل هذا الرجل الثري؟
That's not going to happen.
هذا لن يحدث.
So,
لذا،
you'd better stay away from him!
من الأفضل أن تبتعد عنه!
Are you listening?
هل تسمع؟
I'm summarizing what you said.
أنا ألخص ما قلته.
What's the point of that?
ما الجدوى من ذلك؟
Let me put it simply.
اسمحوا لي أن أضعها ببساطة.
Stay away from him
ابتعد عنه
unless you want to be screwed!
إلا إذا كنت تريد أن تكون مشدودا!
You were so excited
كنت متحمس جدا
that you didn't make yourself clear.
أنك لم توضح نفسك.
I summarized something for you.
لقد لخصت شيء لك.
In the first few minutes,
في الدقائق القليلة الأولى ،
you demonstrated your relationship with him.
أظهرت علاقتك به.
Childhood sweethearts. Families of equal status.
الأحبة في مرحلة الطفولة.  العائلات ذات الوضع المتساوي.
Then you added your achievements.
ثم أضفت إنجازاتك.
I failed to congratulate you.
فشلت في تهنئتك.
It had nothing to do with me, though.
لم يكن له علاقة بي ، رغم ذلك.
But what you said next has something to do with me.
لكن ما قلته بعد ذلك له علاقة بي.
If I understand correctly,
تتتتتت،
you're threatening me.
أنت تهددني.
I'm not threatening you,
أنا لا أهددك
but warning you.
لكن يحذرك.
There's no difference.
ليس هناك فرق.
Don't bother!
لا تهتم!
Let me put it simply.
اسمحوا لي أن أضعها ببساطة.
Stay away from him
ابتعد عنه
unless you want to be screwed!
إلا إذا كنت تريد أن تكون مشدودا!
Let me tell you something, too.
دعني أخبرك شيئًا أيضًا.
Whether I'm in a relationship with Ye Juncheng
سواء كنت على علاقة مع يي جونتشنغ
has nothing to do with you.
لا علاقة لك به.
You...
أنت...
Ye Juncheng is independent.
يي جونتشنغ مستقلة.
He chooses what kind of girl he likes.
يختار نوع الفتاة التي يحبها.
No one can manipulate him.
لا أحد يستطيع التلاعب به.
By the way,
على فكرة،
the PPT you made...
PPT الذي صنعته ...
Oh, no.
أوه لا.
The PowerPoint you made...
PowerPoint الذي صنعته ...
It's ugly.
انها قبيحة.
(One equal status is that we make a perfect couple.)
(أحد الأوضاع المتساوية هو أننا نصنع زوجين مثاليين).
Are you listening?
هل تسمع؟
I'm summarizing what you said.
أنا ألخص ما قلته.
(Ye Juncheng) What's the point of that?
(يي جونتشنغ) ما الهدف من ذلك؟
Let me put it simply.
اسمحوا لي أن أضعها ببساطة.
Stay away from him
ابتعد عنه
unless you want to be screwed!
إلا إذا كنت تريد أن تكون مشدودا!
♪You're so perfect my love my love♪
♪ أنت مثالي جدًا حبيبي
♪You hug me and get no longer defensive♪
أنت تعانقني ولم تعد دفاعيًا ♪
♪I hide the roses behind me♪
♪ أخفي الورود خلفي ♪
♪Stop for you at the street corner oh oh♪
♪ توقف من أجلك عند زاوية الشارع أوه أوه ♪
(All rights of network communication reserved by Tencent)
(جميع حقوق اتصالات الشبكة محفوظة لشركة Tencent)